(732) 407-9253 johnreda4@gmail.com LinkedIn | Portfolio

JOHN REDA

Web Developer - User Experience Designer

A desire to continuously learn and understand what drives a strong humandevice interaction has led me to seek a position as an entry-level user experience designer. With 6 years of experience combining art and technology, I have a solid foundation on which to build, and I aim to expand my knowledge on a daily basis.

SKILLS

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Visual Design ● ● Wireframing ● ● ● Prototyping ● ● ● ● User Personas ● ● ● O Information Architecture ● ● ● ○ Usability Testing ● ● ● ○ User Research ● ● ● Heuristic Evaluation ● ● ●

HTML ● ● ● CSS • • • • JavaScript ● ● ● O

Responsive Design ● ● ● ○ Drupal 7 ● ● ● ○ Wordpress ● ● ● O

SOFTWARE

ios • • • • Adobe Creative Suite ● ● ● ● Sketch ● ● ● O Google Apps ● ● ● O Balsamiq ● ● ● O Windows 10 ● ● ● O Microsoft Office ● ● ● O Windows 10 ● ● ● O

ADDITIONAL

Crucial decision making through the use of critical thinking and deductive reasoning

> Creative thinker who is passionate about quality

Quick learner with ability to work in a dynamic environment Rutgers University | Web Developer Piscataway, NJ / July 2017-Present

• Led project team to overhaul web communications for the largest administrative unit within Rutgers University

- · Responsible for developing information architecture, interface design and development, and user experience design on a project that streamlined the organization's web presence by consolidating 23 individual unit websites into a solitary, centralized website
- Redesigned divisional newsletter; provided graphic design overhaul, provided high quality photography and oversaw the incorporation of videography to establish a digital version of the communication
- Designed departmental reports and informational and promotional materials

Rutgers University | Unit Computing Specialist

Piscataway, NJ / January 2017-July 2017

- Provided desktop support for the second largest organizational unit (2,000+ users) at Rutgers University
- Diagnosed and resolved a wide array of end-user issues
- Created documentation for Standard Operating Procedures

Apple I Apple Certified Mac Technician (Genius)

Bridgewater, NJ / Sep 2013-Present

- Provided customer support by managing daily queues of 250–350 technical appointments
- · Diagnosed end user issues with devices across the entire Apple product line
- · Administered peer training workshops on proper customer engagement and the importance of positioning
- Performed on-site hardware and software repairs for computers and mobile devices
- · Maintained brand awareness by promoting features and benefits of products

EDUCATION

Master of Business & Science

User Experience Design Rutgers University | Expected Completion May 2019

Bachelor of Fine Arts

Photography Rutgers University I May 2014

Certificate

Full-Stack Web Development